structural op occurrences {'continuousStatic': 563, 'attackCost': 543, 'noop': 1810}
combos {('continuousStatic',): 543, ('attackCost', 'continuousStatic'): 15, ('attackCost',): 522, ('noop',): 1800, ('attackCost', 'noop'): 6, ('continuousStatic', 'noop'): 4}

--- continuousStatic samples ---
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may attach 1 Water Energy card to 1 of your Water Pokémon. (This doesn't use
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may turn all Energy attached to Charizard into Fire Energy for the rest of t
P Whenever your opponent's attack damages Machamp (even if Machamp is Knocked Out), this power does 10 damage to the attacking Pokémon. (Don't
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may take 1 Grass Energy card attached to 1 of your Pokémon and attach it to 
P Snorlax can't become Asleep, Confused, Paralyzed, or Poisoned. This power can't be used if Snorlax is already Asleep, Confused, or Paralyzed
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may change the type of Venomoth to the type of any other Pokémon in play other than Colorles
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may flip a coin. If heads, remove 1 damage counter from 1 of your Pokémon. This power can't 
P Snorlax can't become Asleep, Confused, Paralyzed, or Poisoned. This power can't be used if Snorlax is already Asleep, Confused, or Paralyzed
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may change the type of Venomoth to the type of any other Pokémon in play other than Colorles
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may flip a coin. If heads, remove 1 damage counter from 1 of your Pokémon. This power can't 
P As long as Dodrio is Benched, pay Colorless less to retreat your Active Pokémon.
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may look at one of the following: the top card of either player's deck, a random card from y
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may move 1 damage counter from 1 of your opponent's Pokémon to another (even if it would Kno
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may move 1 damage counter from 1 of your opponent's Pokémon to another (even if it would Kno
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may attach 1 Water Energy card to 1 of your Water Pokémon. (This doesn't use
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may turn all Energy attached to Charizard into Fire Energy for the rest of t
P As often as you like during your turn (before your attack), you may take 1 Grass Energy card attached to 1 of your Pokémon and attach it to 
P Snorlax can't become Asleep, Confused, Paralyzed, or Poisoned. This power can't be used if Snorlax is already Asleep, Confused, or Paralyzed
P Once during your turn (before your attack), you may change the type of Venomoth to the type of any other Pokémon in play other than Colorles
P As long as Dodrio is Benched, pay Colorless less to retreat your Active Pokémon.

--- attackCost samples ---
A Discard 2 Energy cards attached to Charizard in order to use this attack.
A Discard 1 Psychic Energy card attached to Mewtwo in order to prevent all effects of attacks, including damage, done to Mewtwo during your op
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Ninetales in order to use this attack.
A Discard all Energy cards attached to Zapdos in order to use this attack.
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Arcanine in order to use this attack.
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Charmeleon in order to use this attack.
A Flip a coin. If tails, this attack does nothing. Either way, you can't use this attack again as long as Farfetch'd stays in play (even putti
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Magmar in order to use this attack.
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Charmander in order to use this attack.
A Discard 1 Psychic Energy card attached to Gastly in order to use this attack. If a Pokémon Knocks Out Gastly during your opponent's next tur
A Flip a coin. If tails, this attack does nothing.
A Discard 1 Fire Energy card attached to Flareon in order to use this attack.

--- noop-only cards (sample) ---
Here Comes Team Rocket! TR 15 | Each player plays with his or her Prize cards face up for the rest of the game.
Here Comes Team Rocket! TR 71 | Each player plays with his or her Prize cards face up for the rest of the game.
Challenge! TR 74 | Ask your opponent if he or she accepts your challenge. If your opponent declines (or if both Benches
Challenge! G2 106 | Ask your opponent if he or she accepts your challenge. If your opponent declines (or if both Benches
Lucky Stadium BP 41 | This card stays in play when you play it. Discard this card if another Stadium card comes into play.
Pokémon Tower BP 42 | This card stays in play when you play it. Discard this card if another Stadium card comes into play.
Plume Fossil FFI 82 | Look at the bottom 7 cards of your deck. You may reveal an Archen you find there and put it onto you
Rare Candy FFI 85 | Choose 1 of your Basic Pokémon in play. If you have a Stage 2 card in your hand that evolves from th
